{
    "data": {
        "7Va1T": {
            "question": "This is a test",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "965586984250785802",
            "answers": {
                "17guV": {
                    "answer": "This is an anwer to a test",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                }
            }
        },
        "9o4ze": {
            "question": "eek",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "965615140072468500",
            "answers": {
                "b6RK3": {
                    "answer": "answer",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                }
            },
            "question_history": [
                "question"
            ]
        },
        "jZ1z2": {
            "question": "jejej",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "question_history": [
                "question",
                "ejejk"
            ],
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "7l5XQ": {
            "question": "This is an example!",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "91wig": {
            "question": "Example question",
            "author_id": "806141455616704573",
            "message_id": "none",
            "answers": {
                "8B4oX": {
                    "answer": "Here's an example answer",
                    "author_id": 618082876730376202
                }
            },
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "moderator"
        },
        "10MGB": {
            "question": "test from mobile device",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "50pOk": {
            "question": "This is a test for the web viewer",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "answers": {
                "c8m8G": {
                    "answer": "Answer 1",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                },
                "2UHT4": {
                    "answer": "Answer 2",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                },
                "1Hs5n": {
                    "answer": "Answer 3",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                }
            },
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "2GI7M": {
            "question": "tets",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "answers": {
                "mx8Q9": {
                    "answer": "gehe",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573
                }
            },
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "58PbL": {
            "question": "test",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "answers": {
                "94VaA": {
                    "answer": "Test",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034"
                }
            },
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "test": {
            "question": "This question is for testing purposes",
            "author_id": "806141455616704573",
            "message_id": "none",
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "moderator"
        },
        "Q2iw2": {
            "question": "test",
            "author_id": "806141455616704573",
            "message_id": "969273717408550974",
            "author": "dante_nl 2#4034",
            "answers": {
                "Rh92v": {
                    "answer": "tet",
                    "author_id": 618082876730376202,
                    "author": "dante_nl#1234"
                }
            }
        },
        "mod_del": {
            "question": "This question has been deleted by a moderator",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "moderator"
        },
        "self_del": {
            "question": "This question has been deleted by the author",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "none",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "deleted": "true",
            "deleted_reason": "author"
        },
        "no_ans": {
            "question": "This question has no answers",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "969276207931731999",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234"
        },
        "with_ans": {
            "question": "This question has answers",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "969276416023752796",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "answers": {
                "h98px": {
                    "answer": "This is the first answer",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034"
                },
                "7NGa0": {
                    "answer": "This is the second answer",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034"
                },
                "Zm61Q": {
                    "answer": "And this is the final one; the third! :D",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034"
                }
            }
        },
        "edit_test": {
            "question": "This question is edited",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "969279925079121960",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "question_history": [
                "This question will be edited"
            ]
        },
        "testing_id": {
            "question": "test",
            "author_id": "618082876730376202",
            "message_id": "969907890552967260",
            "author": "dante_nl#1234",
            "answers": {
                "62DuW": {
                    "answer": "best",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034",
                    "message_id": 969907954134425641,
                    "best_answer": "true"
                },
                "71SNj": {
                    "answer": "worst",
                    "author_id": 806141455616704573,
                    "author": "dante_nl 2#4034",
                    "message_id": 969907974174806026,
                    "best_answer": "false"
                }
            }
    },
    "all_deleted_questions_clears": 4,
    "trusted_people": [
        806141455616704573,
        618082876730376202
    ]
}
